So let's do a critical thinking exercise.
If a business is black owned, what does it need to do to be considered for black people?
Or is just existing as a business owned by black people enough?
Sister Seals, this is your ancestor, Harriet Tubman.
I am Clarissa Tubman! I am Clarissa Tubman!
Coretta had called the girls like, what y'all wearin' to the march?
What y'all wearin' to the march?
I tell her, I was MC Checkerhole!
But now I'm your father.
Oh, chill baby, chill.
It helps her go to sleep, it helps her go to sleep.
Baby, divide and conquer is also about keeping you apart from your soul.
It's also no coincidence that some of our greatest icons of liberation
made Palestine an incredibly important part of their platform.
I'm your father.
We are stardust floating up!